Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
The 749 Research...
...Center for Life Sciences.
also known as Department 749.
manages five research
bases and numerous...
...laboratories across the country.
Since its founding. it has...
...been used for
all investigations.
responsible for mysterious...
...occurrences and has thereby
Remarkable results were achieved.
THE FOLLOWING
STORY IS FICTIONAL. ANY...
...RELATING TO REAL LIFE
IS PURELY COINCIDENTAL.
749 INTERNAL PRIVACY TOP...
...SECRET - ACCESS PROHIBITED
FILE NUMBER 0036502
ZHONGNAN. HONGKUANG CITY Am 5. Juni
An accident occurred
in the Red Mine.
As you can see. the slope gives...
...way and drags
everything with it.
47 miners lost their lives.
We wait anxiously...
The rescue operation lasted...
...seven days. One
miner was rescued.
According to his statement.
he stole while on the run.
onto a previously
undiscovered hollow.
There he arrived with...
...unknown biological spores.
Remains of birds and numerous...
...strange metal
fragments in contact.
The incident was...
...classified as top secret.
and taken over by...
...the authority in 749.
Eight months later.
the miner suddenly died.
His unborn child
also had deformities.
The authorities
suspected a connection...
...with the organisms
discovered in the mine.
To prevent further disasters...
...and to rip the population apart.
The authorities decided to...
...permanently seal the mine.
The metal fragments
and bird remains
were transferred to the Red Mine...
...research center
by Authority 749.
to comprehensively study...
...the unknown organism.
SECRET DIVISION 749
Recently. a noticeable white...
...fog has formed at the Red Mine.
After professional examinations
This fog poses no...
...danger to the human body.
Please remain calm.
Attention! An unknown creature...
...has escaped from the Red Mine.
On July 12th at 1:00 PM
A significant number
of larvae were...
...discovered in the Red
Mine for the first time.
749 immediately
mobilized personnel...
...and collected larval samples.
and began experimenting.
Initial results show.
that the organism is first...
...adaptable and resistant.
It can digest metals...
...as well as proteins.
It is capable of
actively hunting...
...prey that is many
times brighter.
Tests have also confirmed.
that it is a highly...
...intelligent organism.
He uses imitation...
...techniques when hunting.
to lure his prey. to
shower and finally...
...to fuck him
precisely and brutally.
Various methods...
...were tested to destroy it.
Not a single one was
a success. It is more...
...dangerous than any
other living being.
Further investigations
were carried...
...out in the Red
Mine on July 15th.
Retract! Retract! Quickly!
The team's dog was...
...killed in the incident.
The organism was given...
...the name "Creature Zero".
The authorities were informed...
...immediately. To prevent
escape and spread
To prevent creature zero...
...from emerging. Authority 749
Ma Shan. the descendants...
...of the 1992 disaster.
who is to assist with the research.
You have been notified.
Get a plane for Shan.
He's always wanted to see...
...the sea. Bring him to Xiamen.
I have a friend there. And...
...please hurry. Understood?
He doesn't love me at all. he's...
...never been interested in me...
It's okay. sweetheart. don't...
...cry. It'll be alright. won't it?
- Auntie. - Come to me.
Don't drink so much.
I'm interested in you.
Come with me to my place.
we'll continue drinking there.
- Let's go. - Get down from there.
Hands off! What's
the meaning of this?
Just you wait. I'll
wring your neck!
Get lost. you idiot!
It doesn't always get on my nerves.
Hey. are you deaf? I'm not kidding!
See you later. Sule.
I'm going to
rip your head off...
...and then make
mincemeat out of you!
You'll see. then
you'll call me Uncle!
You damned...
...little bastard! Damn...
Shan! Shan! Come here immediately!
I'm sorry. Father.
Who are you
calling Father here?
You should keep your...
...distance. shouldn't you?
I...I didn't want any of this.
Haven't you caused
enough trouble...
...already? People
are already talking.
Should everyone know?
Pack your things.
you're flying today.
Where am I supposed to go?
To the south. You...
...wanted to go to the sea.
And if I don't want to?
Why not?
Your gift is not ready yet.
What is that supposed to be?
That will be a surprise.
Have you already looked at it?
Of course not.
You like to tinker around.
Did you take your medicine?
How much more
time do you need?
Maybe three or four days.
I give you at most two more days.
Look. three unknown...
...cars are driving up!
What do you want here?
- Who are these guys? - Shan! Shan!
Hey. Shan! Quick. come with me!
- Shan! - Beeilung!
Where do you want to go?
Hurry up! Quickly!
What's wrong?
Go with her. let's go!
And don't forget your medicine!
You've broken in. boss!
Come with me!
Search everything. go!
Yes. indeed.
Where is Shan?
I don't. because I'm not.
Who are you? Are
you from the police?
Ask your boss.
No. stop. you're not...
...allowed in there! Hey!
Shan's room is
upstairs. Let's go!
Yes. sir.
- Finds his skateboard. - Okay.
There's nobody here. Boss!
Shan is no longer...
...here. Remove the tarp.
Yes. What is that?
Stop! Woe betide
you if you touch it!
Who do you think you are?
Isn't it obvious who...
...we are? Down with it!
What kind of thing is that?
I have no idea. A tin chicken?
Boss. he's gone.
Let's go.
This isn't over yet.
Bestétige. Shan
fllichtet in ein Auto.
Block all units.
exits two and four.
Understood. Team A in position.
Please get off.
You need to continue
your journey by train.
Take this with you.
Don't drink so much. okay?
Hurry up.
Hey. wait!
Shan is on his way to the city.
The goal is just a click away.
Team Whiskey in Position.
The target is trapped.
Hey. listen up!
- Hey. - A thief!
Come on. guys. grab him!
- Hey! - Man. watch out!
What's the point of that?
Not so reckless!
Are you serious!?
Don't rumble
through here like that!...
Why the rush?
Quick. you can come...
...back up! God. come on!
- Give me your hand! - There he is!
One two three.
four. flinf.
Only five seconds to get...
...across the bridge with Uber.
But to get rid of them.
I will probably
have to run forever.
Where is he?
The trams have been shut down.
He's taking the subway now.
Have you completely
lost your mind?
Why? What's the problem?
Don't guide him
onto the subway!?
Is that a reason to
yell at me like that?
Tell me. what's the problem?
Why shouldn't he
take the subway?
Tall? Tall?
Who are you?
Where are we going?
You already know.
30 kilometers to go...
...until train 749 reaches.
We are there.
Welcome back to 749.
Let through!
Stop it.
Why aren't you
saying anything?
- You're stupid. - Say something!
Come on. man.
Hey. what's that all about?
- Are you deaf? - Give that back!
Stop bothering him immediately!
Does your girlfriend
need to help you?
Now you'll really
get a beating.
Defend yourself...
Or are you too cowardly?
- Shan is back! - What. really?
- Hey. man! - That was ages ago.
"They still remember you."...
...Our Usain Bolt. that's a fact.
Hello!
Is that really necessary?
This is going to
cause trouble again.
Welcome back!
Show him!
Welcome home!
Come on. come down here!
This time it won't
be so easy for him.
Yes.
That motivates us even more.
He'll give us wings.
Come on. let's go to training!
Hey. Chief Qiao
isn't in a good mood.
Boss. Hua is back.
Put the phone in there.
Boss. Ma Shan is here.
Sit down.
What do you actually want from me?
A small favor.
You wanted to leave me alone.
That was a promise.
I didn't work here then.
Are you kidding me?
Hey. hey. hey. Where
are your manners?
Excuse me.
Calm down. kid. I'm new here.
I just want to get to know you.
I couldn't care less.
Your Aunt Sun distills alcohol.
your uncle evades taxes.
Talk to me or I'll expose them.
Now listen to me! I...
...am the one you want.
Don't drag the others into this!
If you help me now. I will...
...leave the three of you in peace.
And what do you want?
Come on. put him in a suit.
DISINFECTION CHAMBERS
Chen. listen to this.
It's almost deciphered.
"Almost" isn't enough.
Isn't that Shan?
- Leave me alone! - Qi. stop!
This is just an
exercise. Don't worry.
Give it here. I'll look after it.
I'm waiting for you.
Inspection complete!
Yes! Pull back!
- The machine is ready. - Good.
Let's get started.
Begin.
- There. here we go! - Here we go!
Test system initialized.
Stage one initiated.
Temperature 36.1...
...°C. Vital signs normal.
Increase intensity. level two.
Increase intensity. level three.
Heart rate 88. Blood...
...pressure 82 over 125.
Temperature 36.5...
...°C. Heart rate normal.
Something is still
holding him back.
Heart rate 90. Temperature rising.
Vital signs remain...
...within the normal range.
Stage five.
Hey Fei. what are you doing?
This is work. take it seriously.
Understood. I'll take it easier.
Shan is in the air.
Temperature 37.2 °C. Heart rate...
...is rising. Vital
signs are normal.
Initiate final test.
Heart rate is now
at 120. and rising.
Heart rate 125. still rising.
Heart rate exceeds 150. 170.
- Chief. - Chief.
Chen. why hasn't
anything happened?
We're already
on the fifth stage.
That should trigger the mutation.
Shan's temperature
is rising rapidly.
Heart rate extremely high. Blood...
...pressure close
to the upper limit.
Last time he destroyed...
...one of our buildings.
This is the Shan we are bending.
His heart rate
is rising again.
Yes. I see it.
What else can we do?
We can't do anything more.
That's enough for...
...today. If we continue.
That could have killed him.
Heart rate at 160. 190.
"What's that going to be?"...
...Fei. carry on.
Qiao...
Temperature at 40 °C. 42.
45. Heart rate at 200!
Are you kidding me?
There's only one Shan!
- Don't stop! - Stop it!
Now we have the real Shan.
I am not a scientist.
But he's back.
I want today's recordings.
All.
Shan is unconscious. No...
...heartbeat. vital signs low.
Prepare for CPR.
Come on. quickly...
I'm sorry. what?
His wounds have all healed.
That is definitely not normal.
Dr. Zhang. That
was in Shan's pocket.
Shan.
Did you get up with
the wrong Fulham?
Let's talk.
Shan. Shan!
He is in corridor 3.
Calm down. kid.
Let me out! Let me out. let me out!
There's nothing to discuss!
Shan. I...
Boss...
Make sure he
gets back on his feet.
We are running out of time.
Creature Zero has grown...
...rapidly in the past week.
It's only a matter of time...
...before she leaves the mine.
got into the city and...
...completely destroyed everything.
Then comes the province. finally...
...the whole country.
and after that...
Enough. We have...
...asked the authorities to
to seal off the city and...
...evacuate the residents.
It'll be alright again.
SPECIAL GIFTED CLASS
Boss. Shan is in the newspaper.
Someone's
looking for a fight.
You file a missing person report...
...and I keep calling
his cell phone.
But I never get a signal.
Where the hell is he?
He can't make phone calls anyway.
What do you mean? Do...
...you know where he is?
They will bring him back.
Who is "she"? And where...
...have they taken him to?
What are you hiding from me?
We know how Shan...
...controls his mutations.
Its strontium exhibits a...
...strong resonance maximum.
Just look.
Here. his bottle.
It contains strontium.
This inhibits enzyme...
...interactions with
their substrates.
Thus. its mutation remains dormant.
So someone administered...
...an inhibitor to him.
to suppress his mutation.
They are better
than the previous...
...bosses. At least
they have intuition.
Instead of education. or what?
Do you know how long...
...the construction took?
30 years.
The mountain was completely looted.
I came here on
my first day of work.
Then I helped dig tunnels.
In 1988. an Olférder
town in Xinjiang...
...was attacked by
unknown creatures.
749 dispatched a
reconnaissance force.
We lost five men.
Twenty years ago.
we discovered the...
...winged creatures under the mine.
But you should already...
...be familiar with them.
These creatures are a...
...completely new life form.
They can digest not only proteins.
but also metals.
Do you know this creature?
No.
"What are you doing?" - "Stop it!"
Can't you hear what...
...I'm saying? Let him go!
Have you completely lost your mind?
Shan.
Let it happen.
You belong to us.
Together we will
wipe out humanity -
the worst virus that
has ever existed.
Destroy humanity.
liberate this planet.
Humans are destined...
...to be destroyed by us.
What did the
creature say to you?
I because} not!
They can't even imagine...
...what the boss was like before.
You'll get used to the...
...current boss's moods.
- Dr. Chen. - Hello.
Dr. Chen.
Is the report finished?
Yes. yesterday.
- Dr. Chen. - Dr. Chen.
I'll put it here.
If you need anything else.
let me know.
Dr. Chen.
Listen...
Yes. yes. that's fine.
Null actually speaks...
...to Shan. unbelievable.
How is that possible?
We intercepted their signals.
and analyzes their frequency.
syllable structure.
and speech rhythm.
This is a fully developed language.
And what does that heal?
Because I'm
not quite sure yet.
It could have been the first...
...contact with an alien species.
If Shan is willing to help...
...us communicate with them.
We can certainly draw...
...on a wealth of resources.
It would then be possible to...
...integrate them and
let them serve us.
They're completely crazy.
Sorry. boss.
Okay. fine.
I will apply for his
residence permit.
Shan should negotiate
his compensation.
but I have to stay here for now.
These fragments were
discovered in the Red...
...Mine along with the
spores of Creature Zero.
I don't want to go in there.
Don't worry. I'll be...
...there for you. okay?
It is a superalloy. far...
...beyond human capabilities.
Activate magnetic system.
We suspect that
these are fragments...
...of the creatures' spaceship.
The creature is restless!
Leave me alone. It's...
...none of my business.
Leave me alone!
The fragments rearrange themselves!
They merge!
It has stopped!
It's out of action!
We did it. yes!
Shut everything down!
- Zhang! - Zhang!
- Zero... - ...is moving again!
These superalloy fragments...
...inhibit Null's activity.
Let me go.
I don't want to become a monster.
Toxic fog streams from the mine...
...and spreads throughout the city.
Furthermore. Null's mass has...
...doubled in the last 48 hours.
We don't have much time left.
Let me through! Look.
where are my birds?
Don't worry. we'll take...
...care of this nuisance.
"Annoyance"? Don't be rude!
Team Whiskey reports that...
...the mutated birds are at the
Collect red mines.
- Herr Qiao.
- Minister Pu.
Their request for a...
...lockdown was rejected.
We need more information...
Okay. okay. Yes. I understand.
I hear?
The press is relieved for now.
Are we going to save your...
...ass every day now? That...
Yes. okay. We're on it.
Your debut is really...
No thank you.
Shan is released again.
And why?
That's wrong. What will...
...become of our research?
We can't proceed...
...any further otherwise.
If we do that. because no...
...one knows where he will go.
That's where you come into play.
Take him to the Red Mine.
Shan won't trust me.
Then gain his trust.
They want to put him back in...
...there so that he
can fully mutate.
Can I help you?
Shan? What are you doing here?
Tomorrow at 2:35 PM we...
...will simulate an evacuation.
All access points will be opened.
Shan will escape.
Come quickly!
We don't have time.
Los. Beeilung!
If he walks past your...
...room. you stop him.
Save me!
All exits of Authority...
...749 will be monitored.
All but one. we'll...
...leave that one open.
I know another way...
...we can get out of here.
Above the laboratory in...
...Zone 6. at
staircase 2 is exit F.
He drives directly...
...onto a mountain road.
Take him there.
- Get the car. - Yes. boss.
Ms. Liu.
Team Whiskey should run away.
Come on!
- Where is Shan? - I have no idea.
- Do you want to? - Let me through!
Dr. Chen. Han is
leaving with a team.
Do we really have
to go there too?
I need to keep an eye on...
...Qiao. He's a real monster.
Okay. I'll call for reinforcements.
All units on standby!
Team Whiskey. advance to...
...the Red Mine.
All units on alert!
A truck!
Stop!
Please stop!
Please. hey!
And who are you?
Dongbei Qiao. Behoérde 749.
You are Comrade Ma Jue.
They were chief scientists at 749.
Or am I wrong about that?
Their task was to monitor the mine.
and Shan for us to study.
Shan. hey!...
Shan! Hello. Shan!...
Where have you been?
Your uncle and
I were so worried.
I'm fine.
Where is my uncle? I...
...urgently need to speak to him.
A little later. yes?
She is a friend.
So what do you want?
I just want to know.
which exactly is its...
...connection to Creature Zero.
And you will help me with that.
Dr. Chen. aren't we much...
...too close to the mine?
How else are we
supposed to see them?
Where is Hans' team?
Team 1 is in
position on the bridge.
And Team 27?
Team 2. are you in position?
Team 2 in Position.
- Hey! - Hey. wait!
Dr. Wu!
Come back!
What's wrong. Shan?
Team 1. observation point.
The creature is clearly agitated!
What was in it?
A painkiller
with electrolytes.
That will kill him.
No. I'll make him
stronger than ever before.
Dr. Wu. please be careful!
Don't worry.
Null hasn't attacked any humans...
...yet. That's a rare opportunity.
I need to get closer.
Team 2 also noticed
increasing unrest.
I can see it.
Yes. me too. Get out of here!
No. we need the data first.
- Team 2. retreat! Go! - Yes!
Dr. Zhang... Drive.
- Drive. go! - No!
Hey. Shan. are you a butterfly now?
Take a picture!
Are you satisfied now?
- Access. - Understood.
Hey. what's that all about?
Shan!
Move aside!
- After you! Stop!
You monster. monster!
Fly away. you freak!
"Shan. Shan. wing on! A...
...chicken that can't fly at all!"
Shan. Shan. flying mold! Flying...
...freaks don't get into heaven!
Shan. Shan. fly on! A...
...chicken that can't fly at all!
Shan. Shan. flying
gray! Flagellant...
...freaks don't get into heaven!
Where are you going? You...
...can't show up looking like that!
Stop. no photos!
Put down your cell phones!
Leave him alone! Stop it!
Go away! Stop filming!
Shan!
Put those cell phones
away immediately!
- Shan! Shan! I'm here! - Aunt Sun!
- I'm here! - Uncle! Uncle!
I'm here! Shan! Get out!
Uncle! Aunt!
Quick. you have
to get out of here!
Leave my son alone!
Stop filming! Put
your phones down!
Look at him!
Please. Shan!
Delete all videos and photos.
Yes...
- Chief. - Chief.
That was good work.
Don't be such a baby.
- Print. - Yes!
Sit back down.
Are you feeling better now. Shan?
These cages were
built for monsters!
How could you treat Shan like that?
I wonder. is he human or a monster?
Do you know exactly?
What are you talking about?
No.
Shan. you are a monster!
Hua. are you okay?
I'm okay. Shan.
Stay here. Wait. Shan!
They eat from the office table.
but they're
spoiling our plans.
I have always
remained true to 749.
What do you give him?
Is that how you show loyalty?
The inhibitor that Shan drinks.
not only suppresses
its own mutation.
but also the growth
of creature zero.
It just didn't work.
In three hours
The city will be sealed off.
Everyone is being evacuated.
You better too.
I still have a mission.
As you already know. you remember!
- Where is Shan? - He's fled.
On the way back to 749.
Why does it have to...
...be Shan in particular?
Tell me.
My boy will not
return alive. will he?
Is this important?
If we can save millions...
...of lives with this.
At 749. it's worth every sacrifice.
Help me find him.
And how is that supposed to work?
He has a tracking device.
Attention. all residents of Birger.
An emergency evacuation...
...is being initiated.
We are coordinating
the safe relocation...
...of all persons to
the assembly points.
Shan.
I thought you were here.
Auntie and you. you must leave.
And why?
Because it will come out.
Why are you so
afraid of your wings?
I want to be normal.
But you're not normal!
Shan.
I've kept something from you.
I have all these years
749 never really left.
I was always a part of it.
"What are you talking about?"
I thought 749 had let us go.
Unfortunately. that's not true.
I only brought you here.
so that you are closer to the mine.
So that I can get...
...to know you better...
...can study.
Yes.
Understand.
Father!
Chief. the first evacuees have...
...arrived in the reception area.
- and will be tested. - Understood.
The military has established a...
...defensive line towards the city.
We don't need the military.
The country has
invested huge sums in...
...the construction
of the laboratory.
We can earn our daily bread here.
And now the military is...
...supposed to get involved too?
Aren't you ashamed?
Let the military
withdraw; it can't...
...do anything against
creature zero.
Why should there be...
...senseless sacrifices?
I have requested that we use our...
...last weapon
against the creature.
And if it doesn't work?
What do you suggest?
Did Cao manage
to get out of the mine?
He didn't want to leave it.
Result?
Are you on your way to Shan?
Only he can convince Cao.
Shan now has wings. How...
...do you intend to find him?
I can do it.
Be sure to tell him.
I'm sorry.
And that we will no longer...
...look for him. He is free now.
The entire city area of ​​the Red...
...Mine has been
completely evacuated.
Staying in the restricted...
...area is strictly prohibited.
Any violation will be punished...
Is anyone here?
The entire city area of ​​the Red...
...Mine has been
completely evacuated.
Staying in the restricted...
...area is strictly prohibited.
Any transgression...
Who are you?
Hello. I'm from the...
...historic preservation office.
Do you know that
there was an evacuation?
I still have to
finish cleaning here.
Hua. Null has reached the city.
Be careful. we're guiding you.
Understood.
Zero makes its way...
...through the city towards 749.
Have you all made your wills?
Yes...
Null is after the alloy...
...fragments of 749.
You should leave now.
I'm so sorry. Shan.
They only did that.
because they are convinced...
...that you can save the city.
Why me? Why?
Your father was the only...
...survivor of the
Red Mine disaster.
Your special ability could...
...be attributed to his encounter
with these unknown creatures.
Where are my parents?
Have you locked them up too?
Your parents died...
...immediately after your birth.
Why? Why did they...
...leave me here all alone?
Because I'm different
from the others?
Because I'm a monster!?
No. that's not true. Shan.
You just used
me and lied to me!
You're forcing me to be a hero.
As if my life were meaningless.
What about what I want?
You want to take
me with you. don't...
...you? Come on! Come
on! Come and get me!
I will never work with you.
I don't want to bring you back.
Your uncle needs
to be evacuated. and...
...only you can
convince him of that.
Never. he's a liar.
How could you say
something like that?
He's in a wheelchair because...
...of you. There's no one...
who loves you more!
Where is my uncle now?
He is still at the shaft.
Uncle? Where are you?
I had already prayed that I...
...would never hear
your voice again.
Have you and your
aunt been evacuated?
I'm not leaving.
Are you angry with me?
How could I be angry with you?
Shan.
You've been holding a...
...grudge all these years.
That was the happiest...
...time of my entire life.
Once you accidentally
called me Dad.
You were so terribly embarrassed.
But I was very happy.
You need to get
out of there. please.
Shan.
Don't be afraid of your feathers.
With you
Even the deepest abyss...
...becomes an infinite expanse.
Do what you have to do. kid.
We will see each other again.
Uncle.
Uncle! Uncle!
Qiao. I because you are...
...currently going to hdren.
Leave the boy in peace. I'll stay.
I will do everything I can.
to give you as much
time as possible.
Farewell. my comrades.
I will miss you.
Look who's here!
Now you monster will perish!
Let's go through with it!
Zero has withdrawn everywhere.
I will come back to you.
Qiao. Qiao. look at this!
The birds gather
at Shan's position.
They are trying to...
...prevent him from returning.
Another swarm is
flying towards 749.
Prepare for battle.
Qiao.
Qiao. where are you going?
Let's see if someone...
...as uneducated as me.
can look after the base.
We're getting out!
Give me your hand!
Highest alert level!
Defense systems activated!
Hold your ground!
Don't let them through!
Assume combat formation.
Clear the airspace.
Hua. Shan. we're
taking you home now.
Fire free!
Airspace is restricted.
Initiate recovery operation.
Defense breached!
Qiao. the inhibitor. indulges!
Get out of there!
Boss. fly ahead. I'll...
...find you some work.
Take care.
- Good work. - Always a pleasure.
Boss. I can't do it. Goodbye!
- Shan! - We've got her. Go back.
Airspace 749 has been reached.
How much time do we have left?
The defense has collapsed;...
...749 units are almost wiped out.
Activate Team Whiskey.
Team Whiskey. you are
the last line of defense...
...of Behoérde 749.
If you fail.
We must use our
weapon of last resort.
However. you all know very...
...well what that
means for the city.
Our country and our
people mean wild.
Your weapons are...
...equipped with inhibitors.
to temporarily halt the zero.
In the history of 749. 28 heroes...
...made the ultimate sacrifice.
You were once the children of 749
And now you shall
become our heroes.
I implore each and
every one of you:
Fight for 749.
Fight for the people.
My only request:
Hold the line until Shan...
...has completed his mission.
I hope we all see each other again.
You can do it!
Activate the magnetic field!
Magnetic field activated.
Dr. Chen. Hua. It's up to you now.
Please keep fighting.
Beschlitzt 749.
Shan.
Please forgive me.
Go away Chef!
Chen. Creature Zero is...
...about to reach
the train station!
Assembly is underway:
39 percent. 40 percent.
The building is at zero!
Protect your data!
Secure your escape!
Explosive balls are...
...tinned! They have no effect!
Current assembly
progress: 83 percent.
Power outage.
magnetic field decreasing!
Okay. the power supply!
Activate the backup power!
Secure the magnetic field!
Backup power active!
92 percent. 93 percent.
Shan. all we need
is one more stick!
Zero has the last fragment!
Fruit!
I'm not important!
Hurry up. quickly!
You must escape!
Give me the kernel.
If you cheat on me.
you'll lose her. Forever.
You are one of us.
Obey us and the
world will be yours.
Are you coming after us?
You will lose everyone...
...you love. As well as your life.
01192 has reached the drop zone.
Attack protocol
is being initiated.
Shan.
Ma Shan.
The ultrasound
shows abnormalities...
...on both shoulder
blades of the fetus.
We recommend an abortion.
He could endanger your...
...life. Please sign here.
It must be a malformation.
Mama.
I heard his voice.
I'm having this baby.
One day the whole
world will realize.
that my child is chosen.
Zero destroyed itself.
Abort attack. return to base.
Understood.
Qiao.
Shan did it.
Hey. Hua. Your
Shan actually did it.
He did it.
Don't be afraid of...
...the wings inside you.
With them. even the deepest...
...abyss becomes
an infinite expanse.
A FEW YEARS LATER
THE RISED PEOPLE
Mom. how can people have...
...wings? That's not true at all.
Humans have always had wings.
I'll explain it to you at home.
Okay.
The world leaves
me full of scars.
but from these
wounds wings grow.
Project funded by the...
...Beijing Cultural Fund
March 2016. pre-production
October 2018. start of filming
Chongqing
China Film Huairou Studio
Baiyin
Karry Wang. 19 - Ren...
...Min. 19 Guests in Need 749
An American Oscar winner.
Neither money nor effort...
...was spared for this tin chicken.
Life-threatening stunts.
She was the first to dare.
At the end of 2018.
the money ran out. and...
...the international
team had to leave us.
But this nice gentleman...
...then helped us. free of charge.
Young Chinese men started filming.
Hordes
Filming in Baiyin was...
...completed in July 2019.
We must win this war. even if...
...it's with millet
and rusty rifles.
Wrap filming for Karry Wang.
Turning point for Li
Chen and Li Meng.
End of filming for Ren Min.
September 2019 What...
...if the guns go on strike?
What do we do when...
...even the millet runs out?
Chengdu
Huairou
Xishuangbanna
Peking
Garze
Quanzhou
Kubugqi-Wuste
2020. filming of...
...countless commercials.
2022 - 2024. further...
...filming. All for financing.
The visual effects were...
...created in 15 countries.
South Korean
Finland
Spain
Australia
Russia
Grol3britannien
deer
China
September 24. 2024. completion.
It is certainly a strong one.
to be born naked and defenseless...
...and yet be adequately nourished.
to stand up for one's
own convictions.
For me. however
It probably simply means...
...that it is enough to be full.
Dedicated to the
6.526 participants.
who contributed
to the film between...
...March 5. 2016 and
September 24. 2024.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today